"You are free to come and go~"
Little boy, it's not that I don't want to save you.
You really have no cure
. Besides, I can't protect myself.
I
can't take care of myself. Don't blame me
. The strong live, and the weak die. Let God decide your life and death.
Yes,
Lu Master ha
ha ha
ha um
, it’s a dawdle,
master Lu, don’t worry
, I’ll definitely return the money to you, what money do you
want
tonight,
you want me to be happy
, ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha
I ’m going , hurry up and reincarnate,
what are you running to die?
Yes,
ah, ah, hahahaha, no, no, what song to sing,
chase ,
chase,
do
n’t run, don’t go
, I’ll give it back to you, do
n’t run, don’t run
, don’t run, don’t
run,
hey, is this just someone’s water?
This is not the carriage of the Lin family Have
you seen him?
Have you never thought about it?
Wow Mr. Li is so handsome,
Mr. Lin,
Mr.
Lin,
take
it, eat more,
come , come and chase me
, hahaha,
come , come,
haha, these
are just picked this year Qingming tea
is fragrant
and mellow , please have a good taste, son
, go down first
, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
, you’re so flexible , you pig, you dare to mess with me, pig Tianma, dare to mess
with
me, Lu Tianma, you don’t want to hang around in the universe city
, hum, I’m sinking Jumping around for so many years,
fearless, fearless,
what I hate most is a bully dog ​​like you
, you
are a dog
, you are a dog, you are a dog, you, you, you,
who does the dog
say,
and you , did you
hear him? Haha, dare to play tricks
on me and see that I am overwhelmed by Mount Tai
.
Oh
my god,
this man is so handsome.
He looks at me like this and I feel like I am floating . Hahaha
, take the young master back to Lingfu
. Hey hero,
hero
, don’t go,
hero , stay here You
sign up, the little girl will definitely ask you to repay her favor in the future
.
Hey,
don’t you have a
concave shape, can you
look at this black and black? What am I going to see ? I
haven’t seen any beauties. Don’t be nervous,
girl .
I just want to make a
deal
with you. How
do you know I’m a girl?
Oh ,
I’m careless.
If
he said that, I'm afraid his life would be in danger.
What do you say, my
master, he owes a huge debt again and again. Girl, you know who was the person who fell into Yiranju with you
that day
. Oh, I do
n't
care who he is.
I 'm a chivalrous man.
You
are right, the person who fell with you
that day
is the brother-in-law who is the pilgrimage master. If
he wants to save face in public
, then take the girl into custody and ask her to be executed. It is
unreasonable
to me.
Abyss
, I want
, I want the abyss, help, help, indiscriminate
killing
, help, help, help,
help
, no one can save me, God , I have lived 18 years without a good day,
and now
I am going to lose my head
What did I do wrong?
God, why are you doing this to me ? God, God!
But
if you agree to make a deal with me,
I can not only keep you and your master safe
, but also make you rich and rich
. Why
is it me
because of this jade pendant?
Yupei, I can’t be wrong
, you are the young master of the Lin family, Lin Qinglan
, the young lady of the Shen family
, Shen Mengjun, who is remarried,
and my condition is
that you marry Lin Qinglan.
So you are talking about a deal
, of course you are stupid,
because a piece of jade pendant can marry someone
. But the engagement letter of Lin Qinglan, the only son of the richest man in
Yuzhou,
who owns it, is the future young mistress of the Lin family
, do
you know
that
this jade pendant is not
mine ? It will be Ms. Shen , but
it doesn’t matter how the jade pendant came from
. The important thing
is that the jade pendant
is in your hands.
As long as you agree to cooperate with me
and pretend to be Shen Mengjun
,
I will give you an extra 1,000 taels of gold a year later. How about
1,000 taels of
gold
? Trading,
this is obviously a welfare, okay?
Now there are two paths , life
and death
, it depends on how you choose.
I choose
, hey, stop fighting, hey
,
hey, hey, hey, hard work, hard work, hard work, hahaha,
jump, jump , jump I, I, and I
have nothing to do to you
. Don’t blame it. Hey, hey
, master promises you that you will never gamble again.
Tiaotiao
1,000 taels of gold
will allow us to start a new life
. Tiao Tiao, you must be saved as a teacher.
You If you don’t save Master
, then next time we meet, we can only be in the
emperor
. Haha. Goodbye, Master. We have depended on each other
for 10 years. In the past 10 years,
we have depended on each other
. Although you are addicted to alcohol and gambling, you
often
make me hungry.
The only relative
, for
all this and for you,
I am willing, good boy, come on,
master , master, have
you thought
about it ,
ah,
I am filial, so I will not do anything unreasonable, don’t
worry,
as long as you listen to me, take care
of the Lin family Hold on to the position of the young mistress
and enjoy the food and drink for a year
, then just take the money and leave,
and
me, how can I say that I am also a big girl,
you say that
if the young master Lin tilts his mouth and squints at me,
he is another pervert,
then he will suffer Isn’t it me?
Anyway,
Lin Qinglan is also a famous handsome man in
Yuzhou . Well,
this
is the general situation of Shen Mengjun. Please
take a look and write it down
carefully
.
Or you can say that I recite it
, and I ca
n’t read or write
. Shen Mengjun’s mother is a famous talented woman.
I'm not Shen Mengjun, and
I don't have a talented girl
. Who wants you to ask me to pretend to be
him ? Okay , here I
read. Listen carefully
. Shen Mengjun, the daughter of Emperor Shen Wendi, the
former
prefect of Ezhou
, is 18
years old, the only daughter in the family, Brother Wu , and there is another
one,
yes. There is one more question for me, the last one,
um ,
Young Master Lin is not a fool, will
we be discovered like this?
Hmph, you guessed it right
. He is a fool
. Please miss Shen,
old lady.
Well , it
really is the same as Shen back then My wife is somewhat similar
. They are all
born beauties
. Don’t talk
nonsense.
Cousin and a cousin.
If it’s not
my family, I’m alone . Thank you,
hahaha
, I didn’t ask you these things
. I was just thinking about your mother Hui Zhilan
back then . No one knows
Yuzhou Ezhou , your father is an upright official
, and your son and his father are life-and-death friends
. Since your father resigned and returned to his hometown,
our two families have lost contact . It has been 10 years.
Ah, how are
your parents now? My parents
, hey,
my parents
passed away due to illness a few years ago
, ah,
how could this happen
now the
children are all dead,
ah, Qing’er, his parents were gone a few years ago,
so he left me This old woman is
deserted in this world
. The arrival of the old lady’s cousin and daughter-in-law is a happy event.
You should be
happy.
Hey, grandma
, my brother and I are still here
. We are with you. You are right
. Our Lin family should have a good event. Now
, maybe Chong Chongxi Qing’er’s illness will be healed
. Hahahaha, by the way
, Qing’er is your future husband. He
is an excellent child
. Many strange things have happened to him in the past year
. Grandma,
whoops, this is Cao Cao
Cao Cao will be here hahaha
why is it him,
obedient savior
, is he the one I want to marry
, but he doesn’t look like a fool
, what is he going to do,
is he going to
kiss me in public?
A gift for Meng Jun. Is
this stupid or not
? Hehehe , it’s
him , it’s
him
. Qing’er
is sure
that she is my wife. That's right , hey,
grandma will send someone to organize your wedding right away
, hahaha ,
wedding, wedding, wedding,
hahaha, wedding
, wedding
, it seems that this jade pendant really has a story,
hey ,
I don't know if I jumped into a pit of fire or a puddle of water
No matter what , let’s take one step at a time,
first worship the heaven
and earth, second worship the high hall,
good , good
, husband and wife worship each other,
hahaha
, good , hey, hey
, I just got married like this, I’m so
hot ,
this marriage
is so hard,
I will have experience next time